<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>THE ULTRAVOID</title>
    <description>STORIES FROM THE DISTANT FUTURE</description>
    <link>http://hemangsk.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://hemangsk.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 23:15:39 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 23:15:39 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.2.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oblivion to the Infidelos</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Galaxy: Hegus’dra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Satellite Galaxy: Imro’eth* (the galaxy of iron)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sector: Set-dihex 1141 (protectorate designation)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Planet: Demptoria&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;City: Pezemtpa&lt;/strong&gt; —Capital and seat of government for the Semme’tatra Federation, homeworld to the Ekta’ra&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Daemos Rexus*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How long did it take these people to build those towers? Very fine works of stone and iron. Taller than mountains.&lt;br /&gt;
Only generations of blood and will can raise such things; the blood of ancestors, spent to give a birth right to their descendants.&lt;br /&gt;
And now I come —the Razer Prince*— to ply my trade, to burn that which they have forfeited, and ensure the glory, and honor of the Hyperg’enot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the distance, siege artillery shells, strike a shield that has stood for a million zera’ton (~ 500,000 years). &lt;em&gt;Bom. Bom. Bom.&lt;/em&gt; Every impact lighting up the protective dome with angry branching sparks that split and crawl into the night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each shell, brings this city closer to its destiny, a fate these arrogant &lt;em&gt;Ekta’ra&lt;/em&gt; sealed themselves, when they defied the Emperor Diatas —my father. &lt;em&gt;Bom. Bom. Bom.&lt;/em&gt; The vengeance of my Lion Knights will be brutal. As is fitting for these Ekta’ra who dishonor us with their insolence. My father does not like repeating himself, in his wisdom, mercy leads to repetition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bom. Bom. Bom.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dynast aide, Lotax’vet —the grey— speaks, his translated voice electronic and flat to the prince’s ears. “Lord Prince General, the city shields fall.” As he foretells, a blinding flash encompasses the city; blue-green arcs of energy snap into the air and ground. The sky above the city becomes an iridescent dome which then vanishes with a loud bang.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;SNNCRAAACKSHPOPoppop&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lotax turns slightly to face his master, his metallic form glinting from beneath his hooded robe. “The city is defenseless my lord.” he said.&lt;br /&gt;
“The garrison will fight to the last.” It will be a &lt;em&gt;beautiful&lt;/em&gt;, bloody slaughter…&lt;br /&gt;
“They will my lord. Your Star-Lions* will accommodate their courage. Shall the army continue as planned my Lord Prince?”&lt;br /&gt;
“Yes…tell the arch’battalions* to cease bombardment. I want every nook and escape tunnel intact so that the razka* hunters can flush out &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; the infidelos* vermin.”&lt;br /&gt;
“As you wish my lord” Doors swosh open as Lotax exits to disseminate his orders. Waiting acolyte-adjutants* stand still and silent beyond in the adjutant enclave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ‘eternal’ shields fell within a dunestar (~2 weeks), the Lord Generals will not give Lotax problems carrying out my plan. Ladros, Uthmar, Vi’kete, and the rest of the Lord &lt;em&gt;argent’generals*&lt;/em&gt; didn’t think the shields would fall that quickly. They were right. Until my little mouse that is. Had she not completed her mission, the shields would still stand. I haven’t decided if I should spare her?…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lotax returns from the adjutant enclave were he made the Lord Prince’s will known, the adjutants now in great activity beyond the enclave doors. “All Generals are affirming your orders Lord Prince” he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“As they should. Sev’attendexi*.” Vanix’ferri —the sev’attendexi— replies as she was trained to —in elegant and distinguished Hai’Dre’Cledeshem*. “Yes my glorious Prince?” Such a fine sev’attendexi.&lt;br /&gt;
“I will address the army and my knights.”&lt;br /&gt;
Vanix works the consoles in front of her, with her four arms, opening audio channels to all Hyperg’enot military elements on the planet. Her task complete she says “All-hands, two-way audio established. My radiant Lord Prince may speak when he pleases”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such a good pet, and such a good investment —those extra arms. It is always a thrill to project ones voice to so many champions. Remember what father always says about these times. They fight for blood-honor.&lt;br /&gt;
“Glorious Knights!” The rhythmic pounding of god-hammer gauntlets, war-lances, and his own voice —echoing off of the battlements and the land— fill the command enclave.&lt;br /&gt;
“I CAN HEAR YOU KNIGHTS” The pounding gets louder. The monstrous crashes of the knight’s twenty eight bestere (12 meter) long war-lances against their god-hammer gauntlets, was deafening.&lt;br /&gt;
“These Ekta’ra have no faith in the Diatas!” The din of the war-lances drowns out the chants from the army. The arch’battalions and glorious infantry instead make themselves heard, with bronze and brass war horns, which growled and spit menacing tones to mix with the knight’s crashing of steel.&lt;br /&gt;
“They are ungrateful for the gifts they have on this world, they have rejected my fathers generosity, they dishonor us, by refusing to surrender what is ours.” Shells no longer fall on the city, but the din echoing off the walls alone seems to threaten to flatten the city.&lt;br /&gt;
“Their unbreakable shield is broken, their garrison awaits SLAUGHTER” &lt;em&gt;Hydaaa Hydaaa Hydaaa&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Rexus Revmet Rexus Revmet&lt;/em&gt; Amplified chants for glory of the Hyperg’enot, begin to mix with the pounding god-hammers and blaring siege horns.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Arch’battalions! Bring down that wall!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bom Bom Bom Bom Bom Bom bom&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battalion’s shells land true, and an entire let’con (~2 mile) stretch of ancient wall, blossoms into grey dusty fireballs. As the dust clears it reveals shining buildings of glass and steel beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I Lord Princes Daemos Rexus decree that the Ekta’ra are shaka’infidelos*. Storm this city! Crush what petulant resistance remain! All Ekta’ra; be they adult, infirm, child, or infant! Put them to flame and blade! &lt;em&gt;Tear&lt;/em&gt; into them! Until they are but meat for dogs! Put them to the flame until their bones are but wisps of &lt;em&gt;ash&lt;/em&gt;! Give them death! Give them the &lt;em&gt;freedom&lt;/em&gt; they so desire! When you are done my Knights, whatever is left can beg for slavery or death! Put this city &lt;em&gt;Pezemtpa&lt;/em&gt; to righteous fire! May its name never again be spoken! Hyperg’enot eternal legion! Advance!” Even after Vanix cut the feed, the war cries of the eternal legion still filled the command enclave, only fading with distance as they advanced on the doomed city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They could have given it up piece meal. Instead we will burn everything until the name Ekta’ra is only a memory. The disgraced ground of this planet —Demptoria— will feed many colonies; its mountains will build many shard-cruisers, chariots, war-lances, and god-hammers. Its core will armor them all. We will use whatever is left as slaves and fertilizer. We will take all of it as we please. All of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The Lion-Knights are engaging the city garrison. The infidelos fall quickly. They fall to the last.” Intoned Lotax.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to see them. I want to watch as the legacy of this place dies. “Ready my guard and thunder-talon. I want to be there when the last of them die.”&lt;br /&gt;
“By your will, my Prince.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Glory eternal to the Hyperg’enot. Death and oblivion to the infidelos&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Razer Prince: The War-call* name given to Daemos&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;War-call: A name given to Star-Lion knigts&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daemos Rexus: Full name, Ret’mie Hypa Daemos Tragateus* Razer Lexo* Rexus&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tragateus: Brutal&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lexo: Of the lion*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lion: Refers to the ancient lions of the Dre’cledeshem birthworld known as Burai. Burai lions look much like terran lions and filled much of the same niche.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sev’attendexi: A disgraced member of a Hyperg’enot dynast —not all dynasts have sev’attendexi—, who must serve the rest of their life as the personal assistant of dynast royalty. They are complete slaves to their master, having only as many rights as they are given.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Infidelos: The name given to enemies which must be obliterated on sight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hai’Dre’Cledeshem: The high dialect of the Cledeshem ancestral language&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imro’eth: Long ago —according to the Hyperg’enot Astro’magi— during a galactic collision were at least one galaxy was ancient, iron rich, almost dead, galaxies, the stars that make up Imro’eth were tossed away from the colliding galaxies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Razka: Elite commandos with smaller statures than other warriors and knights. They are famed for the war hounds that aid them in routing out the deepest of entrenched foes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hetr’steel: High strength composite steel.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 03:27:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://hemangsk.github.io/stories/2021/06/08/oblivion-to-the-infidelos.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://hemangsk.github.io/stories/2021/06/08/oblivion-to-the-infidelos.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reformaent</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Galaxy: Gemi’holon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sector: Emhetra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;System: Reg’tiak&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Planet: Vit’os&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Northern polar mountains&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Pirx’vero Botha, exa’legionate trooper, long range infantry support (sniper/medic)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a bug hunt —a primal bug hunt; that’s all we ever get sent on; that’s all us —the expeditionary, the &lt;em&gt;exa’legionate&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hate bug hunts —primal or otherwise—, hive swarmers feel no pain, and dispense it without mercy. On a bug drop, being on overwatch is mostly the same as any other; being a medic is much more difficult. Why are citizens living on this shadt hole of a world anyway? Haven’t seen any greenery, the weather is bad; it matches the landscape. Those clouds don’t look like rain clouds; too hot for water here; lots of lightning; blue, yellow, and white. The bolts extend the sharp angels of the mountain terrain; sometimes in lone strikes, sometimes in rolling volleys. Nature —at least on this world— used the same pallet for its black and grey clouds, as it did for the grey rocks and the shadows they cast. We’ve been in these mountains for half an caldex (~14 hours) scouring the area of the last known position of a lost militia. Haven’t seen a trace. Don’t think anyone expects to find any either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we had been told what to expect, —during pre-drop briefing on the Legionatus drop ship. Commander Ter Hemner had presented the mission intel with his usual faux enthusiasm, and standard extra pauses between phrases he deemed important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hemner: “…LISTEN UP! For extraa intel! Cross-void swarmers! Known in this space as vetaxa’s! Are believed to be swarming! They are capable of jumps in excess of 40 stardex! (~40LY) They are VERY mean and dangerous! They are believed to be responsible for unexplained disappearances! In systems: Matcha’tiak, Hol-dreda, and Eli’par! We are to drop! We are to conduct search and rescue! For Vit’os local militia! The last distress transmission was post fiiive cal cycles! (~ 5 days ago)”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*a few troopers are unable to hide their murmuring thoughts*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;no chance they are still alive&lt;/em&gt; was the gist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“QUIET AND LISTEN. UP. TROOPERS!!….there may still be survivors! I am authorizing extra gunners! And medical! Per squad! Keep your scanners on the horizon for initial intel! Look out for HIVE MOTHERS!! DO NOT ENGAGE IF ENCOUNTERED!! Reemember, the exa’legionate coollects intel! And seeks exfil! IF A QUEEN OR BRAIN IS FOUND! Heeaavy hitters! Will be brought in to deal with…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hemner said more but the intel was clear; command thinks bugs have either eaten, or captured dozens of citizens. We are to search for them and eleminate all hostiles on the planet surface, while the remaining citizens are evacuated. A bug hunt, so, lots of dead bugs, and like any good exa’legionate, keep our eyes on the horizon, for ‘intial intel’; on this drop that would be a sighting of queen or brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coming up on five interdex (~15 hours) down here; long way to go until Hemner pulls us out; he’s kept us boots on the ground for a long time before, several caldex (~days), or until we have contact; be it bug or civilia…. Wait. What is that? Those shadows don’t look like locals; they look spiny and mean. It &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; easy to tell who the enemy is on bug hunts. Raising trooper lead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “Dixo two, movement ahead”&lt;br /&gt;
Dixo: “copy”&lt;br /&gt;
Dixo: “contact ground swarmers”&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;PFump-PFump-PFump-Crck-Crck-Crck BRRapp BRRapp&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch for a help request from the lead…looks like they’ve got it handled. They’re really gunning them down, reporting: 20..21..22 dead swarmers, dont even need grenades, just UHV* exa’bolts. Gotta remember to keep an eye on the rocks above…I can’t see anything with all the interference, are those clouds just ash?. 40….45… guess they aren’t going to let me splat any. No ones gotten nicked…….&lt;em&gt;yet&lt;/em&gt;. 50…58…60. &lt;em&gt;PFump-mpp-mp BRapp-app-ap&lt;/em&gt; *guns silent*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Attack seems over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An amber symbol starts blinking in the upper HUD; the boss wants a casualty status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “Squad I see all green?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each trooper confirms —through their own interface— that they have no injuries; as they do, green dots —one for each of the fourteen troopers— light up in the lower right corner of her HUD..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “Command we are all clear”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commander Ter Hemner should be pleased at our efficiency?&lt;br /&gt;
Not by his tone….&lt;br /&gt;
Hemner: “AIRBORNE INCOMING!”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CRAAACKackkack&lt;/em&gt; *a red icon in her HUD lights, indicating Egor twelve —one of the other two support troopers— is engaging/engaged*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh FUJUT!! where are THEY? There’s one falling, dead, there’s the rest, do I even need to use the scope? Got one lined up; gentle squeeze on the trigger; &lt;em&gt;CRAAACKackkack&lt;/em&gt; “one bolt, one nerve stem”, these bugs are fast, guess that’s what all the wings are for. FujuT! Ajats!  &lt;em&gt;CRAAACKackkack&lt;/em&gt; That one was charging me I think.  &lt;em&gt;CRAAACKackkack&lt;/em&gt; That one definitely was; we seem to have some mutual feelings. &lt;em&gt;CRAAACKackkack&lt;/em&gt; do I need to activate?…yep &lt;em&gt;CRAAACKackkack&lt;/em&gt; Activating distress signal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “I’M GETTING CHARGED”&lt;br /&gt;
 Dixo: “CONCUSSION GRENADES”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;em&gt;BOOOMM BOOOMM BOOOMM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Ummff! Deploying shield, switching to carbine…shadt…Hemner’s gonna kill me when he finds out I dropped my long range bolter…but those &lt;em&gt;BOOOMM BOOOMMM&lt;/em&gt; ajats! Concussion blasts!…&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;em&gt;BOOOMM BOOOMM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Ummppff. More ground swarmers are coming, charging through their dead brethren; doesn’t seem smart.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;em&gt;BOOOMM BOOOMM BOOOMM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dixo: “All contacts terminated”&lt;br /&gt;
Hemner: “Squad Hettra you are all clear”&lt;br /&gt;
Uhhhghh, just breath…the nausea will pass…the war shock symptoms always do…&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Two of the green lights turned blue in the corner of her HUD indicating casualties, another light indicates the commander has set the squad stance to defensive*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like I’m on the clock. Both injured callsigns —Emyatta six, and Raetera eight— are part of the extra gunners we got, haven’t even met them yet. Powering up position translator, I see a good spot with rock cover. Close to one of the injuries; close my eyes, relax, it’ll be quick, &lt;em&gt;BLAAPBANGannggang&lt;/em&gt;. So loud, and bright. Few things put a trooper through a more disorienting experience than a position translation by a standard issue, exa’legionate, location projector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Opening eyes; stowing my carbine; some more nausea —different than before; also something I’ve experienced a thousand times. Wait till I can feel the ground under my feet…ok heading to the injured trooper *one of the blue dots in her HUD starts blinking*; Raetera eight is getting taken care of, one less injured on the field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s my injured trooper, under plenty of cover, starting vital and data download, starting medical scan, checking-in her injury.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Both dots start blinking in her HUD.*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Info downloaded: Semeshea Emyatta, callsign Emyatta six; Sedra’hk’not*, —a tough and resilient gene-nexus— has sustained a deep laceration; from mid abdomen, to mid chest; grazing a few bones; no organs damaged; no major blood vessels damaged. There is so much blood on her, the cut must have bled hard. Whatever hit her, put a really wide gash in her —and her armor. Arrestor foam did its job; seal the wound from the atmosphere, stop all the bleeding. She has two hearts, both beating at an elevated rate; she seems to be in some pain, not enough for an acid wound though, no sign of poisoning. Alright, shield detached, firing mount stakes — &lt;em&gt;pmp&lt;/em&gt; —, activating atmospheric lock out field, medixae kit and wash cooker powered up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “Can you hear me?”&lt;br /&gt;
Her face mask goes from opaque to clear, revealing a green, lightly dotted, smooth skinned face with two purple and black eyes; a well angled hemegeniocx face and head: two eyes, two ears, above a protruding, angular nasal passage, all above a singular mouth. Her dots were a purple like her eyes, and made symmetrical, semi circle patterns on her face and smooth head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One good looking trooper…stay focused Prix…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her mouth is moving, she’s answering, ugh the translator is lagging…&lt;br /&gt;
Shemeshea: “Yes”&lt;br /&gt;
I could get used to that voice, translated or not…&lt;br /&gt;
Prix: “Once the local air has stabilized, I’m going to remove your armor to get a better scan so I can fix you up”&lt;br /&gt;
Shemeshea: “OK doc”&lt;br /&gt;
Prix: “Follow the light with your eyes”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her pupils are dilated, not sure what that means, making a physio query; should do a quick cognitive test while that query runs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “Whats you GN-type?”&lt;br /&gt;
Shemeshea “Sedra’hk’not”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Atmosphere has stabilized enough, ambient temp has come down, accessing her suit, unlocking her armor. Looks like the query is finished; for her, dilated pupils are a pretty standard parasympathetic response. Interesting…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “Your name and callsign?”&lt;br /&gt;
Shemeshea: “Shemeshea Emyatta, callsign Emyatta six”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “alright I’m taking your armor off and going to see how bad this is”&lt;br /&gt;
Shemeshea “OK doc”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is definitely were all the blood came from. Impressive physiology; this Sedra trooper is all taught, limber muscle; a born warrior, those spot patterns are…all over…stay focused Prix. Standard medae’bot wash should do it, just have to calibrate it for her. Medae washes are cooking, just enough time to clean and prep the wound.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “I’ll have something for your pain soon, just have to synthesize it”&lt;br /&gt;
Shemeshea: *nods*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like I got most of the bug bits out, wash should dissolve the rest, mag ointment applied.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “This will sting a bit at first, but should go numb right after”&lt;br /&gt;
Shemeshea: *nods*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sting? Probably feels cool after a laceration with…ohh there was some acid. Definitely should be cooler. Applying the medae wash. According the her gene-nexus data, her body creates cells which can neutralize foreign acid. She is a piece of art, commissioned and rendered for the life of a legionate, not unlike me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “Your wound was a deep laceration, do you know what hit you?”&lt;br /&gt;
Shemeshea: “A flyer, with a talon”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“There was some acid, but your body neutralized it. I’ve applied a medae wash that is rebuilding your tissue. You should be in gunning shape within a setadex (~ 16 minutes) and back to full strength within a cal cycle (~ 1 day). Try to avoid operating heavy weapons until them”&lt;br /&gt;
Shemeshea: “I’ll try not to…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “Any questions?”&lt;br /&gt;
Shemeshea: *shakes her head, her eyes staying on Prix’s face*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her heart rates are going down, vitals are stable, wound is reacting well. Almost time to say goodbye. Those dark eyes; black discs with iris rings that looked made from living dark amethyst; also still dilated; I think it takes more than the pain drugs to explain…oh shadt! How long was I staring at her eyes!?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Might as well say something, as long as shes still checked-in as an injury they had a private channel. Breath deep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “Do you like bunk visitors?”&lt;br /&gt;
She’s looking at me but not saying anything…did she not understand? maybe she’s…&lt;br /&gt;
Shemeshea: “Yes”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whew…okay lets not draw any attention from the bosses. Deactivating atmospheric exclusion field, stowing medi kit, stowing shield.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “Can you get up?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She’s taking my hand; already regaining strength, more than enough to walk again. A rare, easy remediation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her heart rate has gone down more, but still slightly elevated.&lt;br /&gt;
What would she think if she could see my heart rate like I can see hers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s now or never, remember to breath….&lt;br /&gt;
Prix: “Can I visit your bunk sometime?”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why did that sound so awkward?
Time and moments seemed to stretch, conspiring to make me wait as long as possible —no matter how long she took to make up her mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shemeshea: *nods*&lt;br /&gt;
I can’t remember the last time I wanted a ‘yes’ so bad.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prix: “Your clear for battle duty trooper, good luck”&lt;br /&gt;
Shemeshea: “Thanks doc”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I sign off on her returning to duty, her dot stops blinking and turns from blue to green.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shemeshea’s faceplate goes from clear to flat grey, matching the ground and sky; she attaches maga’suture buttons in several places on either side of the gash in her armor. Magautoriom fibers deploy from the buttons; the fibers grasp each other and tighten; the rift of tega’steel plate running up and down her chest and abdomen closes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her defenses restored, she turns and jogs off in the direction of her assigned position, just like I will soon. The remaining blue dot turns green and the commander sets the combat stance to combat ready: patrol. Time to get to high ground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel guilty sometimes —using my position to find companionship, technically a breach of protocol. But I’ve never met a Sedra, and in the legionate, finding someone ‘compatible’ to share a bunk with is very rare. I certainly didn’t expect to find one on this drop. If someone is in a desert, can you blame them for wanting to find a way to water? Maybe the squad has to wait a little longer before moving on…but hey, it gives my patient some more time to rest before returning to eventual-almost-certian-death, and who knows what we are marching into at this point anyway? I seemed to remember, even in my short time in the legionate, a savant-of-war saying “…on &lt;em&gt;occasion&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; strategic value can be gained from &lt;em&gt;waiting&lt;/em&gt;, then taking &lt;em&gt;action&lt;/em&gt;“…or something like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even for me, &lt;em&gt;especially&lt;/em&gt; for me, death is never far. The long night will take me eventually; like it does almost all of the legionate troopers. It might be by a bug, or by a zealot, or by a billion other deadly things, but it will happen, and before it does, I intend to find what comfort I can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UHV: Ultra High Velocity&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 03:27:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://hemangsk.github.io/stories/2021/05/25/reformaent.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://hemangsk.github.io/stories/2021/05/25/reformaent.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Void Borne</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Galaxy: Gemi’holon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sector: Emhetra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;System: Bara’tex&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Shresta Primatt (Void city)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The border of the Erappa(the ‘freeworlds’)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As their shuttle thrusters fired to alter course, Getta’tai and Regma’tai were pushed hard into their seats and Regma could only speak between fights for breath. “this wasn’t a good idea….you are going too fast…our orbit is too low….we’re going to get fined again” Regma’tai complained to her mate and partner “hmpf..whatever” replied Getta’tai, his bright yellow eyes darting between consoles and gauges as he worked the shuttle controls with his slender, dark chen gara hands “you knew if we got stuck behind that &lt;em&gt;Semlous&lt;/em&gt; freighter we could of been floating in mag lock for another ritodex (~11 days)…” Regma left it at that and went back to monitoring the shuttle instruments, if something was going to fail it would be now. A cold death was as close as misjudgment or bad luck Regma’s first father had always said. He also said not to add distracting arguments to that list of hazards, especially ones that could be settled later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getta powered down the thrusters, easing them from their seats and putting the shuttle on its final path to their destination, which was the mega city space station &lt;em&gt;Shresta Primatt&lt;/em&gt; orbiting the gas giant &lt;em&gt;Shresta&lt;/em&gt;. The planet &lt;em&gt;Shresta&lt;/em&gt; itself —which had given the station its name— was a large, hot ball of gas with more than a hundred moons in the &lt;em&gt;Bara’tex&lt;/em&gt; star system. When the ancestors of Getta and Regma first floated to this world they knew it to be a special place, with moons that were bountiful in metals and ices and a large magnetic field….everything a &lt;em&gt;chen gara&lt;/em&gt; (peta’megi, ‘star borne’) needed to thrive and build.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to plentiful resources, Shresta burns with radiation, Regma could feel it like a low, cold tingle giving vigor to her body and bones. More so when they traveled to the city from their home on the far moon. The chen gara had adapted to the cosmic fields in the endless vacuum, and what causes sickness in many firma bound species, gives them life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“looks like we are in range of the supply net signal…” Getta said, without responding Regma powered up the radio antennas and receivers, and downloaded the latest manifests from the logi guilds on the station… “We have a signal. They have everything we need it looks like” Regma said as she scanned the provision guild inventories with some disappointment… “not much fresh fruit though” she said to Getta, making her smooth dark angular face disappointed. Getta responded with regret in his voice “agh, that is unfortunate…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As had become their habit over the 20 adex (~20 years) they had made this journey, once they had a enough com signal to get data streams Getta attempted to raise the station landing towers “…Shresta tower this is cargo shuttle &lt;em&gt;Setak’tai&lt;/em&gt; on apoapsis intercept, requesting public berthing…” After the fourth try the &lt;em&gt;Shresta&lt;/em&gt; landing authority responded “We see you shuttle &lt;em&gt;Setak’tai&lt;/em&gt; at ten interum (1000 seconds) to mag lock, twelve interum to descent…cutting it close shuttle &lt;em&gt;Setak’tai&lt;/em&gt;…” the station continued with instructions to prepare to for docking and, to Regma’s relief no mention of their high speed approach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Shresta Primatt&lt;/em&gt; is a massive, ancient construct of steel and stone finished white in the tradition of the chen gara. It had been built in orbit by the ancestors of Getta and Regma nearly five tekadex (~5,000 years) ago. Then —by its original plans— it had a circumference of ten tekudex (~15 miles) with enough centrifugal habs to house a hundred thousand &lt;em&gt;chen gara&lt;/em&gt;. Over time like many other bastions of the void borne, it had grown with needs and populations. In the time of Regma and Getta &lt;em&gt;Shresta Primatt&lt;/em&gt; is home to millions of souls from thousands of gene-lines and its size is a hundred fold its original. Now it is a great amalgamation of hab sectors, shipyards, foundries, and trade hubs, all inhabited by &lt;em&gt;chen gara&lt;/em&gt; and hundreds of other races and species. As more sections were added, tall spires were built, and those spires were eventually connected by platforms and bridges, and on those were built more towers and platforms, to those were attached workshops and trade sectors, and on top of those still even taller spires were raised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is one of the best examples of a void borne “space mega city” and Regma felt a buzz of pride for her ancestors that built the &lt;em&gt;Shresta Primatt&lt;/em&gt;. Written deep below the spires and foundries on the original section’s hull, the builders wrote the station’s motto on a platinum plate etched in diamond and gold, &lt;em&gt;“In the sky of Shresta this station shines, until the frontier breaks”&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the city is viewed from a higher orbit, it resembles a scalloped plate floating across the brown, red, and white clouds of &lt;em&gt;Shresta&lt;/em&gt;, or, some might say a flower-shaped cookie floating in tea with cream. Viewed from below —the direction from which shuttle &lt;em&gt;Setak’tai&lt;/em&gt; approached— it appears as it is, a massive city floating in the stars with uncountable towers reaching 20 or 30 tekudex (~30-45 miles) or farther into space from the main station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the &lt;em&gt;Setak’tai&lt;/em&gt; approached from below, &lt;em&gt;Shresta Primatt&lt;/em&gt; began to move into the shadow of &lt;em&gt;Shresta&lt;/em&gt;. The sunset bathed the bottom of the station in deep scarlet red followed by the advancing shadow of night. As Regma watched the spectacle of artificial night overtake the brilliant red, and the station lights lit up in its wake, she reached across the the cockpit and grasped Getta’s hand. He grasped back and smiled…it was a rare and beautiful sight that they had only witnessed a handful of times. “I’ll take that as good luck” Getta said, Regma was reminded of an old &lt;em&gt;chen gara&lt;/em&gt; saying &lt;em&gt;“There is much beauty and hardship in the void, do not meet either alone”&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One could tell their whereabouts in Shresta Primatt (or most space cities) by the smell, as soon as the shuttle air locks opened and its air flew out to exchange with the station atmosphere, Regma detected slick grease, acrid fuel, things burning, distant food, subtle rot, and the low smells of the living…she was at the docks…she was home. The clank of their mag boots on the landing deck joined a innumerable chorus of others as they made their way to the landing authority. As they waited for their turn to report to the authority Regma reviewed their supply list which had been written and grouped in no particular order…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;nutrient powder&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;supplement powder&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Food spices&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Water spices&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;? fresh produce&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;? grains&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;carbon smelting powder X50&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;raw carbon stock X400&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;titanium for plating X4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;platinum for plating X2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;gold for plating X2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;plating nozzle small X20&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;plating nozzle large X15&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Drone cores X4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Logic control units X50&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;? Luminal network antennas/transmitters X3&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;? Super Luminal network antennas/transmitters X4 (Senofi Andrex, or Reson Depar if they have)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Power cables&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;.15 cabre x100&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;.20 cabre X2000&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;.60 cabre X100&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Data cable&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;86 remataq/inex X20,000&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Com cable&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;12 remataq/inex X50,000&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fuel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;upherodium x32&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Demondrite x17&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gases&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;oxydrox (60/40 blend) X15&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;hydrogen X6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;helium X4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;xenon X1&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;argon X2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water filters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;2 gauge X40&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;4 gauge X10&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;00 gauge X12&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Air filters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;3 gauge X10&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;6 gauge X10&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time to make the errand list she thought. “which guilds do you want this time?” She asked Getta as they waited in line, after a moment he said “I can get the cables and metals…I know how much you hate the new fabricators…if you get the provisions and the chem guild stuff, and then we can meet at the tech guild for the transmitters” She nodded just as the authority clerk sitting behind security glass called through a speaker “NEXT”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The clerk was a many armed and many eyed ancient Remat’hypa who’s auto translated voice played haltingly through the speaker “what is…your purpose…on…Shresta Primatt?” Getta responded to the traditional bureaucratic welcome “supply run from Andra Palnus, Vetma’rahd”. The clerk responded with the same tempo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;clerk: “are your…supplies…for maintenance or building?”&lt;br /&gt;
Getta: “both”&lt;br /&gt;
clerk: “what…is your…charter?”&lt;br /&gt;
Getta: “citizen, co-custodian, frontier breaker”&lt;br /&gt;
clerk: “and…your companion?”&lt;br /&gt;
Getta: “the same”&lt;br /&gt;
clerk: *after consulting some unseen data* “your shuttle…may have…two caldex cycles…in the…public berth, if you require…housing…visit the…Shresta Primatt…housing authority…read and…give heed to…all warnings…while visiting…Shresta Primatt…an accidental…death…is never far”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Getta was thanking the authority and getting their keys Regma noticed an unusual group of tan and red uniformed station gendarmes gathering at a large airlock. They formed a line encircling the airlock exit, after they had settled into their places the airlock opened and a striking being in black and silver robes walked out flanked by menacing looking black armored escorts. The being was tall with a smooth oval mirrored helmet they did not remove, she thought they were totally bipedal at first, but then she saw a second set of arms moving under their robes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Behind them were more menacing escorts with what looked to be a prisoner with their hands restrained in between two of them. “have you ever seen anything like that?” she asked Getta once he was done with the station clerk. “looks like they’re bringing someone in, maybe a wanted pirate?” Getta offered “who are ‘they’” Regma responded motioning to the tall black and silver clad entity and their escort on the landing deck below “I don’t know…not the legion or protectorate…must be one of those ‘free riders’…or whatever they call themselves…” “hmmm” Regma mused…quickly forgetting them as thoughts of their next task formed in her mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She had tried not to think much about the unpleasant topic but could avoid it no more…she turned to Getta and asked “so…” his sigh and bowed head told her he already knew what she was going to say “…who’s family do we visit first?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 08:17:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://hemangsk.github.io/stories/2021/05/01/the-void-borne.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://hemangsk.github.io/stories/2021/05/01/the-void-borne.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Blood Ghosts of Nexi</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Galaxy: Gemi’holon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sector: Ter’tai’deroga (erappa)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zemo never liked this world…&lt;em&gt;Nexi&lt;/em&gt; it was called. Things had always been odd at this port of call…little things. Mag compasses were mostly useless, even though they shouldn’t be, and gear that was normally reliable had to be constantly reset. All forms of coms were shaky, plagued with static, and prone to channels crossing. If all that was not enough reason for Zemo to be wary of this place, Nexi was a mere two jumps from the protectorate frontier markers and the Ogion hunters and demons beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The people here called themselves the &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; and they said it was not always like this, they said the strangeness started around 20 adex (~ 20 years) ago…their scientists and researchers had never been able to solve the mystery, and instead they coped…and built their tech to be as stable as it could be. He also found the people here odd, and wondered if that had not always been as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of that oddness could not explain their behavior now…without reason or warning they had locked down the port city in which Zemo’s ship the &lt;em&gt;Sera Freedom&lt;/em&gt; had landed, and the government com channels had become a wash of panicked officials relaying orders which they seemed to not understand. The captain had ordered all hands back to the ship and to make preparations to break through and flee the lockdown if needed. The items they had intended to sell he ordered left on the landing deck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some rookie corsairs might think the captain dumb or cowardly for such actions, to them Zemo would say - if he cared to say it - “that is the only way a rogue could live as long as the captain…and being prepared to run lightly in space is always wise…” - if he cared to say it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the bridge of the &lt;em&gt;Sera Freedom&lt;/em&gt; the sensor monitors showed the &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; fleet moving into formations above Nexi. The captain ordered Zemo to use his talents, and tap into the surveillance feeds and find out what has happening. Zemo went to his station and worked quickly, the &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; did not have a mind for security and, through sub-novum interferomance, he was able to assume a trusted identity with ease. “I’m into their civil surveillance net” Zemo said through his translator “look in the western continents…” said the captain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zemo started going through feeds…they were not organized in any way, many were dead static…some were of warehouses, some on streets. Zemo cycled through dozens and dozens of everyday scenes of life on Nexi…warehouse after warehouse…common areas, streets, hab sectors…and more dead signals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At almost his two hundredth feed reconnect Zemo saw something strange, the feed was from a tower overlooking a market area, &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; soldiers in grey and purple uniforms were herding a crowd of civilians from the market and into a street. “captain, you should see this” as the captain walked over a wailing siren from the city began building and reached its crescendo when the captain looked over Zemo’s shoulder to see what the found.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of one of the streets that the soldiers were herding the citizens into, a panic broke out, they could hear desperate screams through the circuit’s audio feed while at the end of the street what looked like a fine pink mist began roiling into the crowed. Zemo watched as the panic became a visible wave moving through the crowd until the street was a surge of &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; running for their life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a few seconds the captain had seen enough and roared “FULL POWER TO THE ENGINES NOW!! take off NOW!!”, everyone obeyed quickly and wordlessly as the fusion powered hyper thrusters spun up. Strapped in at his station Zemo watched on unbelievably.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mist continued its wispy march into the street pulling horrified and screaming &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; into it, their faces going from horror to mortal pain as they were overtaken. As the mist front got closer to the camera it unveiled a scene of bloody slaughter behind it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was total carnage, &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; body parts and pink blood were everywhere, the stone street drained away the blood forming reverse tributaries fed by piles of death. As Zemo’s mind began to grasp what he was seeing, he thought he could see blood jumping and dancing in time with shiny metallic flickers from the mist front before falling as sticky rain. Something was tearing the &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; to pieces and leaving no survivors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I think something invisible is out there” Zemo said, as the thrusters powered up and pushed Zemo hard into his seat, he felt the need to say. “Derehm help us”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 08:17:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://hemangsk.github.io/stories/2021/04/18/the-ghosts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://hemangsk.github.io/stories/2021/04/18/the-ghosts.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
