<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>THE ULTRAVOID</title>
    <description>STORIES FROM THE DISTANT FUTURE</description>
    <link>http://hemangsk.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://hemangsk.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 19:35:27 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 19:35:27 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.2.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Void Borne</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Galaxy: Gemi’holon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sector: Emhetra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;System: Bara’tex&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Shresta Primatt (Void city)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The border of the Erappa&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As their shuttle thrusters fired to alter course, Getta’tai and Regma’tai were pushed hard into their seats and Regma could only speak between fights for breath. “this wasn’t a good idea….you are going too fast…our orbit is too low….we’re going to get fined again” Regma’tai complained to her mate and partner “hmpf..whatever” replied Getta’tai, his bright yellow eyes darting between consoles and gauges as he worked the shuttle controls with his slender, dark chen gara hands “you knew if we got stuck behind that &lt;em&gt;Semlous&lt;/em&gt; freighter we could of been floating in mag lock for another ritodex (~11 days)…” Regma left it at that and went back to monitoring the shuttle instruments, if something was going to fail it would be now. A cold death was as close as misjudgment or bad luck Regma’s first father had always said. He also said not to add distracting arguments to that list of hazards, especially ones that could be settled later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getta powered down the thrusters, easing them from their seats and putting the shuttle on its final path to their destination, which was the mega city space station &lt;em&gt;Shresta Primatt&lt;/em&gt; orbiting the gas giant &lt;em&gt;Shresta&lt;/em&gt;. The planet &lt;em&gt;Shresta&lt;/em&gt; itself —which had given the station its name— was a large, hot ball of gas with more than a hundred moons in the &lt;em&gt;Bara’tex&lt;/em&gt; star system. When the ancestors of Getta and Regma first floated to this world they knew it to be a special place, with moons that were bountiful in metals and ices and a large magnetic field….everything a &lt;em&gt;chen gara&lt;/em&gt; (peta’megi, ‘star borne’) needed to thrive and build.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to plentiful resources, Shresta burns with radiation, Regma could feel it like a low, cold tingle giving vigor to her body and bones. More so when they traveled to the city from their home on the far moon. The chen gara had adapted to the cosmic fields in the endless vacuum, and what causes sickness in many firma bound species, gives them life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“looks we are in range of the supply net signal…” Getta said, without responding Regma powered up the radio antennas and receivers, and downloaded the latest manifests from the logi guilds on the station… “We have a signal. They have everything we need it looks like” Regma said as she scanned the provision guild inventories with some disappointment… “not much fresh fruit though” she said to Getta, making her smooth dark angular face disappointed. Getta responded with regret in his voice “agh, that is unfortunate…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As had become their habit over the 20 adex (~20 years) they had made this journey, once they had a enough com signal to get data streams Getta attempted to raise the station landing towers “…Shresta tower this is cargo shuttle &lt;em&gt;Setak’tai&lt;/em&gt; on apoapsis intercept, requesting public berthing…” After the fourth try the &lt;em&gt;Shresta&lt;/em&gt; landing authority responded “We see you shuttle &lt;em&gt;Setak’tai&lt;/em&gt; at ten interum (1000 seconds) to mag lock, twelve interum to descent…cutting it close shuttle &lt;em&gt;Setak’tai&lt;/em&gt;…” the station continued with instructions to prepare to for docking and, to Regma’s relief no mention of their high speed approach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Shresta Primatt&lt;/em&gt; is a massive, ancient construct of steel and stone finished white in the tradition of the chen gara. It had been built in orbit by the ancestors of Getta and Regma nearly five tekadex (~5,000 years) ago. Then —by its original plans— it had a circumference of ten tekudex (~15 miles) with enough centrifugal habs to house a hundred thousand &lt;em&gt;chen gara&lt;/em&gt;. Over time like many other bastions of the void borne, it had grown with needs and populations. In the time of Regma and Getta &lt;em&gt;Shresta Primatt&lt;/em&gt; is home to millions of souls from thousands of gene-lines and its size is a hundred fold its original. Now it is a great amalgamation of hab sectors, shipyards, foundries, and trade hubs, all inhabited by &lt;em&gt;chen gara&lt;/em&gt; and hundreds of other races and species. As more sections were added, tall spires were built, and those spires were eventually connected by platforms and bridges, and on those were built more towers and platforms, to those were attached workshops and trade sectors, and on top of those still even taller spires were raised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is one of the best examples of a void borne “space mega city” and Regma felt a buzz of pride for her ancestors that built the &lt;em&gt;Shresta Primatt&lt;/em&gt;. Written deep below the spires and foundries on the original section’s hull, the builders wrote the station’s motto on a platinum plate etched in diamond and gold, &lt;em&gt;“In the sky of Shresta this station shines, until the frontier breaks”&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the city is viewed from a higher orbit, it resembles a scalloped plate floating across the brown, red, and white clouds of &lt;em&gt;Shresta&lt;/em&gt;, or, some might say a flower-shaped cookie floating in tea with cream. Viewed from below —the direction from which shuttle &lt;em&gt;Setak’tai&lt;/em&gt; approached— it appears as it is, a massive city floating in the stars with uncountable towers reaching 20 or 30 tekudex (~30-45 miles) or farther into space from the main station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the &lt;em&gt;Setak’tai&lt;/em&gt; approached from below, &lt;em&gt;Shresta Primatt&lt;/em&gt; began to move into the shadow of &lt;em&gt;Shresta&lt;/em&gt;. The sunset bathed the bottom of the station in deep scarlet red followed by the advancing shadow of night. As Regma watched the spectacle of artificial night overtake the brilliant red, and the station lights lit up in its wake, she reached across the the cockpit and grasped Getta’s hand. He grasped back and smiled…it was a rare and beautiful sight that they had only witnessed a handful of times. “I’ll take that as good luck” Getta said, Regma was reminded of an old &lt;em&gt;chen gara&lt;/em&gt; saying &lt;em&gt;“There is much beauty and hardship in the void, do not meet either alone”&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One could tell their whereabouts in Shresta Primatt (or most space cities) by the smell, as soon as the shuttle air locks opened and its air flew out to exchange with the station atmosphere, Regma detected slick grease, acrid fuel, things burning, distant food, subtle rot, and the low smells of the living…she was at the docks…she was home. The clank of their mag boots on the landing deck joined a innumerable chorus of others as they made their way to the landing authority. As they waited for their turn to report to the authority Regma reviewed their supply list which had been written and grouped in no particular order…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;nutrient powder&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;supplement powder&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Food spices&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Water spices&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;? fresh produce&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;? grains&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;carbon smelting powder X50&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;raw carbon stock X400&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;titanium for plating X4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;platinum for plating X2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;gold for plating X2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;plating nozzle small X20&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;plating nozzle large X15&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Drone cores X4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Logic control units X50&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;? Luminal network antennas/transmitters X3&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;? Super Luminal network antennas/transmitters X4 (Senofi Andrex, or Reson Depar if they have)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Power cables&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;.15 cabre x100&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;.20 cabre X2000&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;.60 cabre X100&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Data cable&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;86 remataq/inex X20,000&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Com cable&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;12 remataq/inex X50,000&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fuel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;upherodium x32&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Demondrite x17&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gases&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;oxydrox (60/40 blend) X15&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;hydrogen X6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;helium X4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;xenon X1&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;argon X2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water filters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;2 gauge X40&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;4 gauge X10&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;00 gauge X12&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Air filters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;3 gauge X10&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;6 gauge X10&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time to make the errand list she thought. “which guilds do you want this time?” She asked Getta as they waited in line, after a moment he said “I can get the cables and metals…I know how much you hate the new fabricators…if you get the provisions and the chem guild stuff, and then we can meet at the tech guild for the transmitters” She nodded just as the authority clerk sitting behind security glass called through a speaker “NEXT”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The clerk was a many armed and many eyed ancient Remat’hypa who’s auto translated voice played haltingly through the speaker “what is…your purpose…on…Shresta Primatt?” Getta responded to the traditional bureaucratic welcome “supply run from Andra Palnus, Vetma’rahd”. The clerk responded with the same tempo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;clerk: “are your…supplies…for maintenance or building?”&lt;br /&gt;
Getta: “both”&lt;br /&gt;
clerk: “what…is your…charter?”&lt;br /&gt;
Getta: “citizen, co-custodian, frontier breaker”&lt;br /&gt;
clerk: “and…your companion?”&lt;br /&gt;
Getta: “the same”&lt;br /&gt;
clerk: *after consulting some unseen data* “your shuttle…may have…two caldex cycles…in the…public berth, if you require…housing…visit the…Shresta Primatt…housing authority…read and…give heed to…all warnings…while visiting…Shresta Primatt…an accidental…death…is never far”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Getta was thanking the authority and getting their keys Regma noticed an unusual group of tan and red uniformed station gendarmes gathering at a large airlock. They formed a line encircling the airlock exit, after they had settled into their places the airlock opened and a striking being in black and silver robes walked out flanked by menacing looking black armored escorts. The being was tall with a smooth oval mirrored helmet they did not remove, she thought they were totally bipedal at first, but then she saw a second set of arms moving under their robes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Behind them were more menacing escorts —who’s mag boots sounded loud on the deck unlike their master— with what looked to be a prisoner with their hands restrained in between two of them. “have you ever seen anything like that?” she asked Getta once he was done with the station clerk. “looks like they’re bringing someone in, maybe a wanted pirate?” Getta offered “who are ‘they’” Regma responded motioning to the tall black and silver clad entity and their escort on the landing deck below “I don’t know…not the legion or protectorate…must be one of those ‘free riders’…or whatever they call themselves…” “hmmm” Regma mused…quickly forgetting them as thoughts of their next task formed in her mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She had tried not to think much about the unpleasant topic but could avoid it no more…she turned to Getta and asked “so…” his sigh and bowed head told her he already knew what she was going to say “…who’s family do we visit first?”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 08:17:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://hemangsk.github.io/stories/2021/05/01/the-void-borne.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://hemangsk.github.io/stories/2021/05/01/the-void-borne.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Blood Ghosts of Nexi</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Galaxy: Gemi’holon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sector: Ter’tai’deroga (erappa)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zemo never liked this world…&lt;em&gt;Nexi&lt;/em&gt; it was called. Things had always been odd at this port of call…little things. Mag compasses were mostly useless, even though they shouldn’t be, and gear that was normally reliable had to be constantly reset. All forms of coms were shaky, plagued with static, and prone to channels crossing. If all that was not enough reason for Zemo to be wary of this place, Nexi was a mere two jumps from the protectorate frontier markers and the Ogion hunters and demons beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The people here called themselves the &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; and they said it was not always like this, they said the strangeness started around 20 adex (~ 20 years) ago…their scientists and researchers had never been able to solve the mystery, and instead they coped…and built their tech to be as stable as it could be. He also found the people here odd, and wondered if that had not always been as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of that oddness could not explain their behavior now…without reason or warning they had locked down the port city in which Zemo’s ship the &lt;em&gt;Sera Freedom&lt;/em&gt; had landed, and the government com channels had become a wash of panicked officials relaying orders which they seemed to not understand. The captain had ordered all hands back to the ship and to make preparations to break through and flee the lockdown if needed. The items they had intended to sell he ordered left on the landing deck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some rookie corsairs might think the captain dumb or cowardly for such actions, to them Zemo would say - if he cared to say it - “that is the only way a rogue could live as long as the captain…and being prepared to run lightly in space is always wise…” - if he cared to say it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the bridge of the &lt;em&gt;Sera Freedom&lt;/em&gt; the sensor monitors showed the &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; fleet moving into formations above Nexi. The captain ordered Zemo to use his talents, and tap into the surveillance feeds and find out what has happening. Zemo went to his station and worked quickly, the &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; did not have a mind for security and, through sub-novum interferomance, he was able to assume a trusted identity with ease. “I’m into their civil surveillance net” Zemo said through his translator “look in the western continents…” said the captain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zemo started going through feeds…they were not organized in any way, many were dead static…some were of warehouses, some on streets. Zemo cycled through dozens and dozens of everyday scenes of life on Nexi…warehouse after warehouse…common areas, streets, hab sectors…and more dead signals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At almost his two hundredth feed reconnect Zemo saw something strange, the feed was from a tower overlooking a market area, &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; soldiers in grey and purple uniforms were herding a crowd of civilians from the market and into a street. “captain, you should see this” as the captain walked over a wailing siren from the city began building and reached its crescendo when the captain looked over Zemo’s shoulder to see what the found.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of one of the streets that the soldiers were herding the citizens into, a panic broke out, they could hear desperate screams through the circuit’s audio feed while at the end of the street what looked like a fine pink mist began roiling into the crowed. Zemo watched as the panic became a visible wave moving through the crowd until the street was a surge of &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; running for their life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a few seconds the captain had seen enough and roared “FULL POWER TO THE ENGINES NOW!! take off NOW!!”, everyone obeyed quickly and wordlessly as the fusion powered hyper thrusters spun up. Strapped in at his station Zemo watched on unbelievably.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mist continued its wispy march into the street pulling horrified and screaming &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; into it, their faces going from horror to mortal pain as they were overtaken. As the mist front got closer to the camera it unveiled a scene of bloody slaughter behind it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was total carnage, &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; body parts and pink blood were everywhere, the stone street drained away the blood forming reverse tributaries fed by piles of death. As Zemo’s mind began to grasp what he was seeing, he thought he could see blood jumping and dancing in time with shiny metallic flickers from the mist front before falling as sticky rain. Something was tearing the &lt;em&gt;Dereese&lt;/em&gt; to pieces and leaving no survivors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I think something invisible is out there” Zemo said, as the thrusters powered up and pushed Zemo hard into his seat, he felt the need to say. “Derehm help us”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 08:17:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://hemangsk.github.io/stories/2021/04/18/the-ghosts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://hemangsk.github.io/stories/2021/04/18/the-ghosts.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Stories</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
